It's so beautiful here.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だよ、ここ
So beautiful.
めちゃ綺麗
Isn't it so beautiful?
めちゃ綺麗くない?
So beautiful.
めちゃ綺麗
I wanted to show you.
見せたかったんだよね
I feel like my heart will be clean.
心が綺麗になりそう
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
I tripped on the stairs.
階段でつまづいたわ
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
The water is amazing.
水がすごい
That's amazing.
すごいよね
Isn't it blue?
青いでしょ?
It's blue.
青いです
That's it after all.
やっぱりあれだね
It's small.
狭いね
narrow.
狭い
More and more of that.
どんどんあれやんか
The sound of the river is getting louder.
川の音が大きくなってくるね
fun.
楽しみ
fun?
楽しみ?
fun.
楽しみ
Amazing, this.
すげえ、これ
Is it fun?
楽しいか
There are also chestnuts.
クリとかもあるもん
amazing.
すごい
Isn't this included?
これ入ってるんじゃない?
It's in.
入 ってる
heavy?
重い?
Looks heavy.
重そう
That's not included.
それは入ってないんですよ
this?
これ?
it hurts!
痛い!
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
Isn't it hoppai?
ホッパイじゃない?
Hoppai.
ホッパイ
Can I eat it?
食べれるんかな?
Looks like I'll eat it.
食べそう
This is done.
これができてる
this.
これ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
This is done.
これできてる
Contains 2 pieces.
2個入ってる
Really.
ほんまや
I can't eat it if it turns this color.
こんな色しちゃったら食べられないもん
This way.
こっちや
こっち
I saw something good.
いいの見れたわ
いいの見れた
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗やん
beautiful.
綺麗
transparent.
透明
It's transparent.
透明よね
So good.
すげえいい
Because there are naturally beautiful girls.
自然と美少女がいるから
This is good, isn't it?
これいいですよね
amazing.
すごい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll bring it to you.
持ってあげるんやから
Teacher.
先生さ
Is it because it's Mr. Lee?
リーさんだからか
Shall we go?
行こうか
It was dangerous.
危なかった
I was about to fall.
落ちかけた
It was dangerous.
危なかったね
危なかった
I'll leave your bag for you too.
カバンも置いてあげるよ
This feels really good though.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいんやけどこれ
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
fun.
楽しい
Please stop.
やめてください
receive?
受ける?
receive.
受ける
Isn't it quite fast?
結 構速くない?
fast.
速い
The flow is extremely fast.
流れがめちゃくちゃ速い
It's insanely fast.
めちゃくちゃ速い
I'm going.
行 きます
So fast.
すごい速い
That's terrible.
やばいね
Isn't it dangerous?
やばいんじゃないの?
That's dangerous.
そっち危ないって
I'm going to die.
死んじゃう
yes.
はい
It's hard to dig into this bag.
この荷物なかなか掘らないからさ
Amazing nature.
すごい自然
And there are only two people.
しかも2人やし
There are only two of us.
2人しかいないし
There are only two people.
2人しかいない
Did Ippo do okay?
一歩でやつ大丈夫やった?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
I'm so wet though.
めちゃくちゃ濡れてるんやけど
Okay, so let's make it here.
よし、じゃあここで作っちゃおう
It's also really heavy.
これまためちゃくちゃ重いんだよ
This one.
こいつが
How to make?
作り方?
Shall we make it together?
一緒に作ろうか
Can you make it?
作れる?
I have nothing to make.
作ることないです
Spread it out.
広げて
Shall we sit down?
座ろうか
thank you.
ありがとうございます
That's what I mean.
こう いうところってさ
There's no one there.
誰もいない
Because I can't release it.
解放できないからさ
My teacher is always horny.
ずっと先生ムラムラしてるんやけどさ
Can I just sit there?
そこだけ座っていい?
Yeah.
うん
I can't help it.
仕方ないな
Is it okay?
いいの?
Oh, seriously?
え、マジで?
Is that it?
あれやんか
Mio-chan is also horny, isn't she?
ミオちゃんもムラムラしてたんちゃう?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Really?
ほんま?
I'll check it out.
チェックしますよ
Well then, just a little.
じゃあちょっとさ
Can I take it off from the top?
上から外していっていい?
Shall I take it off then?
じゃあ外しちゃおうか
I saw your underwear earlier.
さっき見えてたからさ、下着は
I know the color though.
色は知ってるんだけどさ
I took it off.
外しちゃって
Is it a sports bra?
スポブラやんか
I did a sports bra.
スポブラやったんや
what?
何?
already.
もう
I hope you won't be disappointed.
期待裏切らへんね
Wow.
うわー
Fair skin!
色白!
Let's stand up to the top.
上まで立っちゃおう
Wow, that's erotic.
うわ、エロい
It's so erotic, so extreme up.
エロいよ、めちゃくちゃ
It's so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロいよ
no,
いや、
Oh dear.
か わいいわ
Aw, that's cute.
わ、かわいいわ
It's moist.
しっとりしてる
You're sweating, after all.
汗ばんでるね、やっぱり
It's a little erotic.
ちょっとエロいね
I stood up right away.
すぐ立ってきた
Look, I got up right away.
ほ ら、すぐ立ってきた
What about this?
こっちは?
I can't stand here.
こっち立てないやん
But, let's sit down for a while.
でもさ、ちょっと座るやん
I'll sit down.
座るよ
Didn't you see this too?
こっちも見えなかった?
Look, I'm standing up.
ほら、立ってきた
It stood up amazingly.
すごい立ってきた
And it's moist though.
そしてしっとりしてるけど
Wow, wow.
うわ、やば
It's sensitive.
感度いいんやね
Wow, that's soft.
うわ、柔らかい
I'm sorry.
たまんね
Raise it up a little bit.
ちょっと上にあげて
That's amazing.
すごいな
It's already silver.
もう銀々になってる
Why this?
なんでこれ?
why?
なんで?
Why is it silver?
なんで銀々になってる?
It might not be very pretty.
めっちゃ綺麗にならないかも
Can I go down too?
下も下っていい?
Well then, this too.
じゃあ、これも
Is this also that?
これもあれか
Wow, I see.
うわ、なるほど
Erotic.
エロー
It's so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロいやん
Seriously, it's so moist.
マジで言ったらしっとりしまくってるわ
Sweat this.
汗これ
Is it sweat?
汗なんかな?
Is it wrong?
違うかな?
Which one?
どっちやろ?
Let's take a peek
ちょっと覗いちゃお
cormorant.
う
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ ー、綺麗
The color is so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ色綺麗し
Hey, raise your leg up a little bit.
ちょっとさ、足そんそん上にあげて
Raise your legs like this.
足をこういうふうに上にあげて
This is also erotic.
これまたエロいわ
I can't stand it.
たまらんね
I can't get enough of it.
たまりません
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Oh no.
やば
Such a beautiful color.
めっちゃ綺麗な色
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
I'm getting really wet.
めっちゃ濡れてきた
It's really warm inside.
めっちゃあったかい中
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I put my finger in?
指入れていい?
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
Shimaru Shimaru.
しまるしまる
Wow, wow.
うわー、やば
Don't get wet today.
濡れやねん、今日中
Are you always thinking about erotic things?
なんだかんだエロいことばっか考えたんちゃうの?
Just a little more, can you put your butt in front of me?
もうちょっとさ、 お尻、前に入れてくれる?
You can put more fingers in it.
指がもっと入れるからさ
Wow, that's erotic.
うわー、エロい
Take it to the side by yourself.
自分でここさ、 横に外して
So that I can see it.
見えるようにさ
Ah, erotic.
あー、エロ
Erotic.
エロ
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
I get really wet though.
めっちゃ濡れるんですけど
difficult?
難しい?
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
It makes me jumpy.
ビクビクするもん
If I was touching it.
触ってたら
If it comes out like this, wait a minute.
こんなに出たらさ、 ちょっと
Damn it, it's slimy.
やば、ぬるぬる
Which one feels better?
どっちのが気持ちいい?
Both feel good.
どっちも気持ちいい
Do both feel good?
どっちも気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
A little slimy.
ちょっとぬるぬる
I hear you can't stand it.
我慢できないなって、 聞いてんけどさ
Can I have you lick me?
舐めてもらっていい?
Yeah.
うん
Sorry, my house.
すみて、うち
Take it home.
うちにしろ
delicious.
おいしい
Erase it.
消せろ
Yeah.
うん
home.
うち
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It's so erotic.
くっちゃエロい
Yeah.
うん
Out of the blue.
うち、あく
Teachers, everyone.
先生の方、みんな
Oh wow, so cute.
あ、すごい、かわいい
home.
うち
a.
あ
Ah, that feels good.
あ、それ気持ちいい
However, it's a little warm.
ただ、ちょっと温かい
Ah, that feels good.
あ、それ気持ちいい
Oh, that, this.
あ、それ、これ
Ah, that feels good.
あ、 それ 気 持ちいい
a.
あ
Oh wow, so cute.
あ、すごい、かわいい
Ah, that's right.
あ、それ、ね
The bottom is also a little long.
下もちょっと長いね
Yeah.
うん
Amazing, bottom.
すごい、下
If I didn't study, I would get better at this word.
勉強しないと、この言葉が うまくなった
Wow, it's so delicious.
すっげー、めちゃうまいね
Yeah.
うん
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
Now, it's below the top.
今、上の方の下ね
Yeah.
うん
Mei-chan, please be nervous.
めいちゃんの方、緊張してね
Ah, you know, that's amazing.
あ、ね、すっげー、ね
terrible.
やばい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Yeah.
うん
Mei-chan, come on.
めいちゃん、さあ
You're so sweet because you're licking my Jesse.
俺のジェシー舐めてるから、 こんなに甘ってる
I thought it was amazing and asked if I could see it.
すごいって、見えるかな、と聞いて
Sorry.
ごめんね
I don't know what's erotic.
エロいことかわからない
I'm here.
きました
It's kind of cute.
なんか、かわいいね
Mr. Fuma.
ふまさん
He looks like that.
そういう顔する
Hello.
こんにちは
Yeah.
うん
Other than that, it felt good.
別に、気持ちよかったね
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
what happened?
どうしたの?
practice.
練習
shoulder?
肩?
Can you ride on my shoulders?
肩に乗れちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Did you manage to ride?
乗れちゃった?
Yeah.
うん
Will you go twice?
2回も行く?
Yeah.
うん
My feet are covered in sand
足、砂だらけになっちゃ
That's it.
って
Shoulders, Stretch out your hands.
肩、 手を伸ばします
Stretch out your shoulders and hands.
肩、手を伸ばします
Isn't it okay?
大丈夫じゃない?